[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The prefix of Greek origin, oto is used in medical terminology to refer to what body part?", "correct_answer": "Ear", "incorrect_answers": ["Nose", "Mouth", "Eye"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the first question Troy Bolton asks in the movie High School Musical?", "correct_answer": "Do I go Left?", "incorrect_answers": ["Do I go Right?", "Do I have to shoot?", "One more time mom?, Please!"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What actor was offered a role in the 2001 animated movie Shrek but turned it down?", "correct_answer": "Robin Williams", "incorrect_answers": ["Ben Stiller", "Adam Sandler", "Robert De Niro"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When is the national holiday called Hispanic Day celebrated annually in Spain?", "correct_answer": "October 12", "incorrect_answers": ["August 15", "December 6", "December 8"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the #1 reason for the rhinos decline worldwide?", "correct_answer": "Poaching", "incorrect_answers": ["Disease", "Farming", "Predators"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Tatum, played by Rose McGowan in the movie Scream, died by being gutted and hung from a tree.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "James Earl Jones, who voiced Darth Vader, also provided the voice of a character in which of the following Disney movies?", "correct_answer": "The Lion King", "incorrect_answers": ["Aladdin", "The Little Mermaid", "Bambi"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what Oklahoma city was the shopping cart invented?", "correct_answer": "Ardmore", "incorrect_answers": ["Guthrie", "Duncan", "Broken Arrow"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these musicians was not among the first class inducted into the Jazz Hall of Fame?", "correct_answer": "Ray Charles", "incorrect_answers": ["Earl Hines", "Benny Carter", "Art Tatum"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what northern country did the Siberian Husky dog breed originate?", "correct_answer": "Russia", "incorrect_answers": ["Norway", "Finland", "Alaska, USA"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these makes Cockatoos different from other parrot species?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["They have a gall bladder.", "They are not so colorful as other parrots.", "They have a headcrest."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The absence of the protein called Christmas factor, a.k.a. factor IX, from the human body results in this serious disease.", "correct_answer": "Hemophilia", "incorrect_answers": ["Parkinsons disease", "Epilepsy", "Diabetes"]}]